{
    "subject": "Emilio_Fern\u00e1ndez",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Pueblerina",
    "human_readable": "Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film Pueblerina.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9296021461486816,
            "question": "Who directed the film Pueblerina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9170618653297424,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9123989939689636,
            "question": "Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez is known for directing which type of film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7709221839904785,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6148438453674316,
            "question": "What is the plot of Pueblerina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6083735227584839,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in Pueblerina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5933504104614258,
            "question": "What impact did Pueblerina have on cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5748157501220703,
            "question": "Where was Pueblerina filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4211750626564026,
            "question": "What year was Pueblerina released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35147160291671753,
            "question": "What genre does Pueblerina belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film Pueblerina.",
            "html": "yago_9206_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Pueblerina released?",
            "html": "yago_9206_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Pueblerina filmed?",
            "html": "yago_9206_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Pueblerina have on cinema?",
            "html": "yago_9206_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9206_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents support that Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film \"Pueblerina,\" as mentioned in multiple entries."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}